{"sport":"Tennis","event":"AUSTRALIAN OPEN ","date":"2013-01-18","people":["Agnieszka Radwanska"],"interview":[{"question":"You haven't dropped a set all season. Is this the best start to a year that you've ever had before?","answer":"Well, I think so. I never played two tournaments before Australian Open. It was my first time I played Auckland and Sydney. I think it was a good start.Well, I can't complain, for sure.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"What's made it so good?","answer":"That's a good question. I don't know. I didn't really change anything.Of course, I was practicing hard in the offseason, a lot of fitness. But just feeling good on court. I'm very confident from the beginning and just happy that I can play really my best tennis from the beginning of the year.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Did you do anything different during the offseason than you didn't do before?","answer":"No, not really, no.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Where do you do your fitness work in the offseason?","answer":"I'm practicing in Poland, in Krakow, where I live. I was practicing indoor. It was winter, minus 10.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"How many weeks did you take off at the end of the year and just not pick up a racquet?","answer":"I had almost three weeks without anything, yeah.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"When did you actually start preparing for the new year?","answer":"I think it was like around 15 or 16th of November. Yeah. So six weeks' preparation before I came here.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"You have practiced indoors obviously because it's too...","answer":"Yes, of course everything indoor. It's not even hard court. It's something a little bit faster than hard court. So, yeah.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"So it's only really practice? You don't do any work in a gym?","answer":"Of course I did a lot of fitness, as well. Of course.But a lot of different stuff, yes.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Would you have maybe preferred a tough three‑set match along the way to guide you exactly with your game, or are you happy to just keep doing it quickly?","answer":"I think it's much better to play just two sets; much fresher for another one. Especially that I think those 12 matches almost in a row. Of course now it's a little bit better because I have a day off after every singles, but it's always better to play short than three hours out there.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"What did you do well today?","answer":"I think I was really solid from the beginning, trying to be focused. Especially in the beginning of the first set I was really tight, and I think that game when I was serving when it was 2‑1, I think it was really important game. I think then I start to play better, and of course in the second set I was trying to, you know, to start good as well and not to lose my focus.That's it, yeah.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Do you feel that you're stepping up your intensity with each match at this tournament?","answer":"Well, I really had a lot of good matches against top players this year, and I must say I'm really playing good and everything is working.Well, I just hope I keep going. Of course now is gonna be harder and harder playing against seeded players.We'll see.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Do you think there is improvement though with each round?","answer":"I think so. The first matches are always tough, especially every tournament is a little bit different, different tennis, different courts. The first one or two matches they're always a little bit different, a little bit tricky.Here the showcourts, center courts, are almost indoor, and then you're playing outside and it's outside with wind. I think you have to be prepared for everything here.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Is this your best winning streak of your career?","answer":"I think so. I think I never win 12 matches in a row, no.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Is 13 an unlucky number in Poland?","answer":"There is. I didn't say that.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Are you superstitious?","answer":"No, not really, no. Not at all, actually.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"What did you do between the end of last season and getting ready for this season?","answer":"I had vacation for almost two weeks. Then I came back to Poland.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"You got away to the sunshine?","answer":"Exactly. I did my third semester in university, so I was studying for one month like very, very hard to finish that. Also practicing, as well. I was pretty busy.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"How do you discipline yourself to study when you've been traveling the world and playing in front of huge crowds? It's two different worlds.","answer":"As I was saying, it's good to know something more than just play forehand, backhand. Of course it was really tough to studying and being professional tennis player. I must say they really help me out and I can do my exam whenever I'm ready. So when I'm ready, I'm just calling them and I'm going to university and having exams. Without a doubt for sure it's impossible to study.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"What are you studying?","answer":"Tourism in the Polish University in Krakow.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"},{"question":"Any thoughts only your next opponent? They're playing now. It's Jankovic or Ivanovic. Will you watch?","answer":"Well, I have a couple of things to do right now, but I know them for long time.Actually, it's very hard to say who's going to win today. But I have played them couple times, both of them. If I'm going to have chance, I will watch as well, yeah.","person":"AGNIESZKA RADWANSKA"}]}